Guide to the Harry Randall: Fifteenth International Brigade Films and Photographs ALBA.PHOTO.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series D: Miscellaneous, September 1937-June 1938; August 1938
  - Photo Unit #: D251 Sign outside Teruel, "Alto A Teruel", Jan 1938 (Item 11-1366)
  - Photo Unit #: D252 Reading and rest room for men of our outfit, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0856)
  - Photo Unit #: D258 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion and civilian fiesta at Tivisa, [seated children], May 1938 (Item 11-1839)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/32)
  - Photo Unit #: D260 After Teruel [4 soldiers sitting against wall, one reading a newspaper], Feb 1938 (Item 11-1367)
  - Photo Unit #: D261 After Teruel, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0857)
  - Photo Unit #: D266 After Teruel, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0858)
  - Photo Unit #: D267 After Teruel, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0859)
  - Photo Unit #: D270 After Teruel, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0860)
  - Photo Unit #: D271 After Teruel, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0861)
  - Photo Unit #: D273 After Teruel, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0862)
  - Photo Unit #: D274 After Teruel, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0863)
  - Photo Unit #: D275 Ambulance, after Teruel, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0864)
  - Photo Unit #: D278 Dental Wagon at work, "Doc" [Jack] Klein, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0865)
  - Photo Unit #: D279 Ambulance, "From the Workers of West Virginia", Feb 1938 (Item 11-1368)
  - Photo Unit #: D280 Ambulance labeled "The West Virginian No. 2"] and drivers [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], Feb 1938 (Item 11-1895)
  - Photo Unit #: D281 Kitchen [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], Feb 1938 (Item 11-1896)
  - Photo Unit #: D285 Recruits at Alcorisa, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1369)
  - Photo Unit #: D289 Earl Browder addressing MacKenzie-Papineau at station near Teruel, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1096)
  - Photo Unit #: D292 Print from captured negative, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1097)
  - Photo Unit #: D295 Men of 59th Battalion who received awards at Christmas time, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1826)
  - Photo Unit #: D296 Football game, 15th Brigade U.S. Alcorisa, Juventud Socialista Unificada, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1098)
  - Photo Unit #: D300 Spectators at football game [including women], Feb 1938 (Item 11-1370)
  - Photo Unit #: D303 Refugio near Lincoln-Washington Battalion kitchen, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1099)
  - Photo Unit #: D304 Cedrilla, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1100)
  - Photo Unit #: D305 Group of Spanish soldiers, on stone steps, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1371)
  - Photo Unit #: D306 Festival, 15th International Brigade, Popular Front, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0866)
  - Photo Unit #: D314 Shelters made by comrades of Company 2, 59th Battalion, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1101)
  - Photo Unit #: D317 15th Brigade Estado Mayor [Headquarters] outside Hijar at retreat, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1102)
  - Photo Unit #: D323 Meeting of Political Commissars of 15th Brigade with Luigi Gallo, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1372)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/22)
  - Photo Unit #: D324 Peasant weaving, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1103)
  - Photo Unit #: D325 Outside Hijar, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1104)
  - Photo Unit #: D326 Group, Genie of 61st Brigade waiting to go to front. Also point of road control. [group at checkpoint, some on ground with piles of gear], Mar 1938 (Item 11-1373)
  - Photo Unit #: D329 Farmlands, Hijar, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1374)
  - Photo Unit #: D331 Repairing clothing, MacKenzie-Papineau, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1105)
  - Photo Unit #: D335 Women and children at Letur, Mar 1937 (Item 11-1375)
  - Photo Unit #: D337 River Letux, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1106)
  - Photo Unit #: D346 Water wheel, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Ebro Front, May 1938 (Item 11-0867)
  - Photo Unit #: D369 [Soldiers, group], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1107)
  - Photo Unit #: D370 [Soldiers, group], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1108)
  - Photo Unit #: D371 [Soldiers, talking], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1109)
  - Photo Unit #: D372 [Three soldiers], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1110)
  - Photo Unit #: D373 [Three soldiers], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1111)
  - Photo Unit #: D377 [At the front], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1112)
  - Photo Unit #: D380 [Officers addressing the troops (?)], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1113)
  - Photo Unit #: D381 [Woman addressing the troops (?)], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1114)
  - Photo Unit #: D387 [Soldiers, group], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1115)
  - Photo Unit #: D390 [Soldiers in a bunker], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1116)
  - Photo Unit #: D393 [Soldiers with auto], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1376)
  - Photo Unit #: D394 [Soldiers with auto], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1377)
  - Photo Unit #: D395 [3 soldiers, 3 women], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1378)
  - Photo Unit #: D396 [Group of soldiers with one woman], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1379)
  - Photo Unit #: D397 [Crowd, a few soldiers, mostly men and women civilians; car in background], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1380)
  - Photo Unit #: D398 [Group of soldiers, same locale as D394, 395, 397], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1381)
  - Photo Unit #: D399 [2 soldiers with bulletin board], May 1938 (Item 11-1382)
  - Photo Unit #: D400 [3 soldiers], May 1938 (Item 11-1383)
  - Photo Unit #: D401 International Brigade Conference, May 1938 (Item 11-1384)
  - Photo Unit #: D402 [Officers addressing the troops], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1117)
  - Photo Unit #: D403 [Officers addressing the troops], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1118)
  - Photo Unit #: D405 [Soldiers, group], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1119)
  - Photo Unit #: D409 [Officers addressing the troops], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1120)
  - Photo Unit #: D410 International Brigade Conference, May 1938 (Item 11-1385)
  - Photo Unit #: D417 [Spaniards (?)], May 1938 (Item 11-1121)
  - Photo Unit #: D422 [Officers addressing the troops], May 1938 (Item 11-1122)
  - Photo Unit #: D424 15th International Brigade [meeting?], May 1938 (Item 11-1760)
    (Moscow Number: 5/177/44)
  - Photo Unit #: D427 [Officers addressing the troops], May 1938 (Item 11-1123)
  - Photo Unit #: D429 [Soldiers marching], May 1938 (Item 11-1124)
  - Photo Unit #: D434 [At attention, staff meeting (?)], May 1938 (Item 11-1125)
  - Photo Unit #: D438 15th International Brigade on watch, [marching on road with flag], May 1938 (Item 11-1761)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/1)
  - Photo Unit #: D439 [Soldiers, marching], May 1938 (Item 11-1126)
  - Photo Unit #: D441 [Officers addressing the troops], May 1938 (Item 11-1127)
  - Photo Unit #: D442 [Officers addressing the troops], May 1938 (Item 11-1128)
  - Photo Unit #: D443 [Soldiers, marching], May 1938 (Item 11-1129)
  - Photo Unit #: D445 [At attention, staff meeting (?)], Jun 1938 (Item 11-1130)
  - Photo Unit #: D446 [Soldiers, marching], May 1938 (Item 11-1131)
  - Photo Unit #: D447 [At attention, staff meeting (?)], May 1938 (Item 11-1132)
  - Photo Unit #: D449 Square in Alcorisa, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1133)
  - Photo Unit #: D451 Fountain in Alcorisa, Jan 1938 (Item 11-0868)
  - Photo Unit #: D452 Fountain in Alcorisa, Jan 1938 (Item 11-0869)
  - Photo Unit #: D454 Showers, Ebro Front, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1386)
  - Photo Unit #: D459 Ambulance from Teachers Union and American Student Union, Murray Nemeroff driving, May 1938 (Item 11-0870)
  - Photo Unit #: D460 Ambulance from Teachers Union and American Student Union, Murray Nemeroff driving, May 1938 (Item 11-0871)
  - Photo Unit #: D462 Campesinos at dance in Valls, May 1938 (Item 11-1134)
  - Photo Unit #: D469 Practicing infiltration: Cabos School, May 1938 (Item 11-1135)
  - Photo Unit #: D472 15th International Brigade School for Cabos, May 1938 (Item 11-1136)
  - Photo Unit #: D475 Hospital at Valls, May 1938 (Item 11-1137)
  - Photo Unit #: D485 British Battalion listening to John Gollan [not visible], Ulldemolins, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1387)
  - Photo Unit #: D486 British Battalion listening to John Gollan, Ulldemolins, May 1938 (Item 11-1138)
  - Photo Unit #: D495 Funeral of Lieutenant William Digges, Mollerusa, May 1938 (Item 11-1139)
  - Photo Unit #: D496 Funeral of Lieutenant William Digges, Mollerusa [soldiers carrying coffin], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1388)
  - Photo Unit #: D497 Funeral of Lieutenant William Digges, Mollerusa, May 1938 (Item 11-1140)
  - Photo Unit #: D498 Funeral of Lieutenant William Digges, Mollerusa, May 1938 (Item 11-1141)
  - Photo Unit #: D499 Funeral of Lieutenant William Digges, Mollerusa [soldiers at graveside], May 1938 (Item 11-1389)
  - Photo Unit #: D506 Activist Congress, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1142)
  - Photo Unit #: D509 Some delegates, Activist Congress, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1143)
  - Photo Unit #: D511 Louis Bortz (Bradely) [?] mail censor, Barcelona, May 1938 (Item 11-1144)
  - Photo Unit #: D513 Fascists taken prisoner (150) Belchite, Sep 1938 (Item 11-1145)
  - Photo Unit #: D514 Fascists taken prisoner (150) Belchite, Sep 1938 (Item 11-1146)
  - Photo Unit #: D515 Fascists taken prisoner (150) Belchite, Sep 1938 (Item 11-1147)
  - Photo Unit #: D516 Fascists taken prisoner (150) Belchite, Sep 1938 (Item 11-1148)
  - Photo Unit #: D518 Refugees from Belchite, Sep 1938 (Item 11-1149)
    (Moscow Number: 5/191/102)
  - Photo Unit #: D523 15th International Brigade on train ride, Valencia, Dec 1937 (Item 11-1150)
  - Photo Unit #: D525 Cabo School, Ebro Front, May 1938 (Item 11-1151)
  - Photo Unit #: D527 Fiesta, MacKenzie-Papineau and civilians at Tivisa, Edward Cecil Smith, David Doran, Frank Rogers, May 13, 1938 (Item 11-1390)
  - Photo Unit #: D545 School for Commissars, Ebro Front, May 1938 (Item 11-1152)
  - Photo Unit #: D546 MacKenzie-Papineau, Hijar, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1391)
  - Photo Unit #: D550 Swim and change of clothes for 15th International Brigade, May 1938 (Item 11-1392)
    (Moscow Number: 5/191/93)
  - Photo Unit #: D556 Football game, 13th and 15th International Brigades, Tarraga, May 1938 (Item 11-1153)
    (Moscow Number: 5/192/1)
  - Photo Unit #: D558 Football game, 13th and 15th International Brigades, Tarraga, May 1938 (Item 11-1154)
  - Photo Unit #: D562 British Battalion machine-gun company, Tarraga, May 1938 (Item 11-1816)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/16)
  - Photo Unit #: D565 Soldiers at Activists Congress, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1155)
  - Photo Unit #: D569 Sanidad [Health], lunch time, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1156)
  - Photo Unit #: D571 Trade Union Delegation at MacKenzie-Papineau, in the vineyards, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1393)
  - Photo Unit #: D577 Recruit group building fortifications, Marca [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], Jun 1938 (Item 11-1897)
  - Photo Unit #: D578 Lincoln-Washington boys with peasants tending vines, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1394)
  - Photo Unit #: D579 MacKenzie-Papineau group marching to vineyards, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1157)
  - Photo Unit #: D582 MacKenzie-Papineau group working in vineyards, Marca, Jun 1938 (Item 11-1198)
  - Photo Unit #: D585 Joseph Brandt of Lincoln-Washington Battalion reading news, Jun 1938 (Item 11-0872)
  - Photo Unit #: D587 Hospital, wounded soldier reading in bed, undated (Item 11-1395)
  - Photo Unit #: D599 Auto Park, Alcover, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1396)
  - Photo Unit #: D600 Volunteer for Liberty, Alcover, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1158)
- Series E: Miscellaneous, 1938-01-1939-09
  Series IIE: Miscellaneous, January 1938 - September 1938. Many of the 761 images in this series capture the final battles of the International Brigades. The most arresting shots are those taken at the crossing of the Ebro in July 1938. In an article that appeared in the Volunteer for Liberty in September 1938, Randall described the Photo Unit's activities and the photographic record they created during the Ebro Offensive:
  "In the period of reorganization and training that preceded our crossing of the Ebro, we were busy snapping pictures of training schools, delegations, fiestas, activities, meetings, classes, congresses, etc. Then the moment came when we prepared to attack. Ben Katine took a fine set of pictures of our comrades crossing the river in boats and rafts of the building of the first footbridge and the first groups of our soldiers to walk across it to the west bank of the Ebro, ours once more. We went ahead with our troops as we advanced, and later made pictures of the ruins of towns bombed by the Fascist planes."
  This series also includes pictures of peasants working in the fields of Marca; the presentation of a flag by Juventud Socialista Unificada (Unified Socialist Youth of the Spanish Communist Party); and the evacuation of wounded in Gandesa.
  - Photo Unit #: E0001 Lincoln Brigade troops marching to North Pole, Teruel Sector [snowy landscape with distant figures], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1397)
  - Photo Unit #: E0002 Company 2, Lincoln-Washington Battalion trench at North Pole, Teruel Sector, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1398)
  - Photo Unit #: E0003 Lincoln-Washington Battalion trench at North Pole, Teruel Sector, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1399)
  - Photo Unit #: E0005 Officers of 15th International Brigade and others at North Pole, Teruel Sector, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1400)
  - Photo Unit #: E0006 Alvin Cohen, action scene, Company 1, Lincoln-Washington Battalion North Pole, Teruel Sector, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1401)
  - Photo Unit #: E0007 Action Scene, Company 2, Lincoln-Washington, North Pole, Teruel Sector, Jan 1938 (Item 11-0064)
  - Photo Unit #: E0008 Spain 1938, scene in Terrega, May 1938 (Item 11-1402)
  - Photo Unit #: E0011 Lincoln-Washington Battalion trench at North Pole, Teruel Sector, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1403)
  - Photo Unit #: E0012 Lincoln-Washington Battalion trench at North Pole, Teruel Sector, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1404)
  - Photo Unit #: E0013 Lincoln-Washington Battalion trench at North Pole, Teruel Sector, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1405)
  - Photo Unit #: E0014 Lincoln-Washington Battalion trench at North Pole, Teruel Sector, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1406)
  - Photo Unit #: E0015 Lincoln-Washington Battalion trench at North Pole, Teruel Sector, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1407)
  - Photo Unit #: E0016 Lincoln-Washington Battalion trench at North Pole, Teruel Sector, Jan 1938 (Item 11-0065)
  - Photo Unit #: E0017 Lincoln-Washington digging Battalion trench at North Pole, Teruel Sector, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1408)
  - Photo Unit #: E0019 Lincoln-Washington Battalion trench at North Pole, Teruel Sector, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1409)
  - Photo Unit #: E0020 Lincoln-Washington Battalion marching to Teruel Sector, Jan 1938 (Item 11-0066)
  - Photo Unit #: E0022 Lincoln-Washington Battalion trench at North Pole, Teruel Sector, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1410)
  - Photo Unit #: E0023 Captain Leonard Lamb and Captain Milton Wolff of Lincoln-Washington Battalion at North Pole, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1411)
  - Photo Unit #: E0024 Action Scene, Company 1, Lincoln-Washington Battalion at North Pole, Teruel, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1412)
  - Photo Unit #: E0025 Action Scene, Company 1, Lincoln-Washington Battalion at North Pole, Teruel, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1413)
  - Photo Unit #: E0026 Machine-Gun Company 1, Lincoln-Washington Battalion at North Pole, Teruel, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1414)
  - Photo Unit #: E0031 Truck pulling anti-tank gun at Cuevas Labradas, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1415)
  - Photo Unit #: E0033 Brigade officers near Teruel, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1416)
  - Photo Unit #: E0035 Brigade officers near Teruel, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1417)
  - Photo Unit #: E0036 Dugout at Brigade Estado Mayor [Headquarters] near Teruel, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1418)
  - Photo Unit #: E0039 WalterCallion, chauffeur and Auto Park mechanic near Teruel, Jan 1938 (Item 11-0067)
  - Photo Unit #: E0041 Dr. Edward Barsky and Dr. Weiss [?] at Hyar, Dec 1937 (Item 11-0068)
  - Photo Unit #: E0046 Robert Minor, Major Robert Merriman and Earl Browder at Valverde, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1419)
  - Photo Unit #: E0047 Major Robert Merriman and Earl Browder at Valverde, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0069)
  - Photo Unit #: E0049 [Soldiers at train tracks], undated (Item 11-0070)
  - Photo Unit #: E0050 Crowd entertained by accordion, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1420)
  - Photo Unit #: E0052 [Two soldiers], undated (Item 11-1421)
  - Photo Unit #: E0053 Lincoln-Washington Battalion Trench, North Pole, Teruel Sector, Jan 1938 (Item 11-0071)
  - Photo Unit #: E0056 [Two soldiers with their shoes off], undated (Item 11-1422)
  - Photo Unit #: E0057 Brigade marching out of Seguro after being relieved, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0072)
  - Photo Unit #: E0061 After marching out of Seguro de Los Baños after being relieved, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1423)
  - Photo Unit #: E0065 Transmiciones [Transmissions] at Seguro de Los Baños, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1424)
  - Photo Unit #: E0066 [Soldiers, group], undated (Item 11-1425)
  - Photo Unit #: E0070 [Soldiers, fortification], undated (Item 11-1426)
  - Photo Unit #: E0073 Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic at observation post at Seguro de Los Baños, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1427)
  - Photo Unit #: E0075 Digging Spanish comrades out of wreckage after Fascist bombing at Seguro de Los Baños, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1428)
  - Photo Unit #: E0076 Digging Spanish comrades out of wreckage after Fascist bombing at Seguro de Los Baños, [dead soldier], Feb 1938 (Item 11-1429)
  - Photo Unit #: E0077 Digging Spanish comrades out of wreckage after Fascist bombing at Seguro de Los Baños, [carrying body], Feb 1938 (Item 11-1430)
  - Photo Unit #: E0079 Digging Spanish comrades out of wreckage after Fascist bombing at Seguro de Los Baños, [carrying wounded man], Feb 1938 (Item 11-1431)
  - Photo Unit #: E0082 Max Bowers, chauffeur, [and ?], undated (Item 11-1432)
  - Photo Unit #: E0083 Teniente Steve Tsermengas and autos at Hijar, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1433)
  - Photo Unit #: E0089 Retreat from Hijar to Caspe, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1434)
  - Photo Unit #: E0091 Retreat from Hijar to Caspe, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0073)
  - Photo Unit #: E0092 Runners organized for retreat through mountains to Caspe, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1435)
  - Photo Unit #: E0094 Resting while retreat to Caspe is organized, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1436)
  - Photo Unit #: E0096 MacKenzie-Papineau or Lincoln-Washington Battalion organized for march to Caspe, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1437)
  - Photo Unit #: E0097 MacKenzie-Papineau or Lincoln-Washington Battalion organized for march to Caspe, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1438)
  - Photo Unit #: E0098 March through hills to Caspe, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1439)
  - Photo Unit #: E0100 Cavalry patrol on march to Caspe, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1440)
  - Photo Unit #: E0101 March through hills to Caspe, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1441)
  - Photo Unit #: E0103 March through hills to Caspe, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1442)
  - Photo Unit #: E0104 March through hills to Caspe, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1443)
  - Photo Unit #: E0106 A rest during march to Caspe, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0074)
  - Photo Unit #: E0107 A drink of water during the march to Caspe, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1444)
  - Photo Unit #: E0111 Brigade Auto Park at Mora la Nueva, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1445)
  - Photo Unit #: E0112 Brigade Auto Park at Mora la Nueva, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0075)
  - Photo Unit #: E0113 Repairing a motor at 15th International Brigade garage, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1446)
  - Photo Unit #: E0114 Brigade Auto Park at Mora la Nueva, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1447)
  - Photo Unit #: E0116 Auto Park kitchen at Mora la Nueva, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1448)
  - Photo Unit #: E0117 Joseph North at Auto Park at Mora la Nueva, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1449)
  - Photo Unit #: E0118 Joseph North at Auto Park at Mora la Nueva, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1450)
  - Photo Unit #: E0119 Civilians building refugios, Mora de Ebro, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1452)
  - Photo Unit #: E0121 Evacuation of civilians, Mora de Ebro, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1453)
  - Photo Unit #: E0122 Evacuation of civilians, Mora de Ebro, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1454)
  - Photo Unit #: E0123 Sound Truck at British Battalion at Batea, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0264)
  - Photo Unit #: E0124 Sound Truck at British Battalion at Batea [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], Mar 1938 (Item 11-1898)
  - Photo Unit #: E0140 Major Robert Merriman, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Batea, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0265)
  - Photo Unit #: E0147 15th International Brigade delegation and Unión General de Trabajadores officials at textile factory in Barcelona, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0076)
  - Photo Unit #: E0148 15th International Brigade delegation and Unión General de Trabajadores officials at munitions factory in Barcelona, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1455)
  - Photo Unit #: E0149 15th International Brigade delegation and Unión General de Trabajadores officials at textile factory in Barcelona, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1456)
  - Photo Unit #: E0151 15th International Brigade delegation and Unión General de Trabajadores officials at textile factory in Barcelona, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1457)
  - Photo Unit #: E0153 15th International Brigade delegation and Unión General de Trabajadores officials at textile factory in Barcelona, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1458)
  - Photo Unit #: E0155 A Barcelona street, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1459)
  - Photo Unit #: E0156 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion canteen, Ebro Front, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1850)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/57)
  - Photo Unit #: E0164 Popular Front Delegation and 15th International Brigade soldiers, Falset, Apr 14, 1938 (Item 11-0266)
  - Photo Unit #: E0166 Boys of "Pioneers" at 15th International Brigade, Falset, Apr 14, 1938 (Item 11-0267)
  - Photo Unit #: E0169 Popular front delegation at MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Ebro Front [group under a tree; man holding a newspaper talks to several women], Apr 14, 1938 (Item 11-1460)
  - Photo Unit #: E0170 Wall newspaper and Popular Front delegations at MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Ebro Front, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1828)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/3)
  - Photo Unit #: E0171 Popular front delegation at MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Ebro Front [group in front of bulletin board], Apr 14, 1938 (Item 11-1461)
  - Photo Unit #: E0172 John Gates and MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Ebro Front, Apr 14, 1938 (Item 11-0268)
  - Photo Unit #: E0176 Delegates of Popular Front from nearby village speaking at celebration in MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Apr 1938 (Item 11-1851)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/62)
  - Photo Unit #: E0178 Frank Rogers speaking at festival, Ebro Front, Apr 14, 1938 (Item 11-1462)
  - Photo Unit #: E0179 Frank Migone, José María Varela, John Rossen, and [?], Ebro Front, Apr 1938 (Item 11-0269)
  - Photo Unit #: E0182 [Soldiers distributing mail], undated (Item 11-1463)
  - Photo Unit #: E0183 [Soldiers with mail], undated (Item 11-1464)
  - Photo Unit #: E0184 [Soldiers with mail], undated (Item 11-1465)
  - Photo Unit #: E0189 Estado Mayor [Headquarters] kitchen, Jack Cooper in foreground, Valverde, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1466)
  - Photo Unit #: E0191 Ruins, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1467)
  - Photo Unit #: E0200 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Batea [troops sitting on ground], Mar 1938 (Item 11-1468)
  - Photo Unit #: E0205 Staff compiling records, MacKenzie-Papineau, Batea, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0270)
  - Photo Unit #: E0212 Brigade Sanidad [Health] School, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0271)
  - Photo Unit #: E0213 Frank Dorsey and Frank Migoni Flores, Comisariado [Commissariat], Batea, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0272)
  - Photo Unit #: E0218 David Doran awarding citation for merit, undated (Item 11-1469)
  - Photo Unit #: E0219 Presentation of award to Steve Tsermengas, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0273)
  - Photo Unit #: E0221 Burt Jackson, Thomas Page, Joseph Taylor, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0274)
  - Photo Unit #: E0222 Comrades building fortifications, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0275)
  - Photo Unit #: E0225 A chabola [shelter], Mar 1938 (Item 11-0276)
  - Photo Unit #: E0228 Stretcher-bearer class, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0277)
  - Photo Unit #: E0229 Eluard Luchell McDaniels, Batea, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0278)
  - Photo Unit #: E0232 Observers and Mappers School, Mar 1938 (Item 11-0279)
  - Photo Unit #: E0233 [Soldiers, group], Mar 1938 (Item 11-0280)
  - Photo Unit #: E0234 [Soldiers, group], Mar 1938 (Item 11-0281)
  - Photo Unit #: E0235 [Soldiers, relaxing/reading newspapers], Mar 1938 (Item 11-0282)
  - Photo Unit #: E0236 [Soldiers, relaxing/reading newspapers], Mar 1938 (Item 11-0283)
  - Photo Unit #: E0237 [Soldier, reading newspaper], Mar 1938 (Item 11-0284)
  - Photo Unit #: E0238 [Soldiers, group], Mar 1938 (Item 11-0285)